To really get people to really pay attention to your presentation, bring up themselves.
Everybody likes it when they talk about themselves.
You might want to first start off with.
Hey, do you want to know what you?re made out of?
You?re made out of six elements, per say, that are from the table of elements, the periodic table that is.
Did you know that there is oxygen in your body?
Did you know that you have carbon, hydrogen, nitrogen, calcium and phosphorous?
All those different combinations make up a human being, which is you and oh, by the way your an animal.
Did you know that?
So if you point that out to people and show them what your all made out of, it's quite a interesting spectrum and it makes you so human, it really does.
So there you have it, elements in our daily lives.
Your periodic table.
Simple presentations, some decorations and don't get me wrong you can add to it up here.
You can put little things here, you might even put a little clay-do up there, but anything to make it interesting or three dimensional.
You might even put the clay-do man up here, but there you have.
It's just a very simple science presentation.